{"questions":[{"question":"Requirementss validation techniques are:","level":2,"answers":["Requirements reviews","Prototyping","All the answers are correct","Test-case generation"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":3},{"question":"Which of these are basic operationsin software engineering?","level":1,"answers":["Software specification","Software development","Software validation","All the answers are correct"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":4},{"question":"What is the basic parts of design pattern?","level":2,"answers":["Problem - Name","Consequences and trade-offs of application - solution - Problem - Name","Solution - Problem","Solution - Problem - Name"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Which of the following are from the advantages of MVC?","level":1,"answers":["One point of view","Multiple views","Clarity of design","The answers 2 & 3 are correct"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":4},{"question":"Software can be tested as :","level":2,"answers":["Black Box","White box","The answers 1 & 2 are correct","There is no correct answers"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":3},{"question":"Technically, correctness is :","level":3,"answers":["Not Feasible - Not neccessary - Not sufficient","Feasible - neccessary - sufficient","Not Feasible - neccessary - Not sufficient","Feasible - Not neccessary - sufficient"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":1},{"question":"Stages of testing are :","level":3,"answers":["Discover testing - Release testing - user testing","Development testing - Release testing - user testing","Validation testing - Discover testing ","Validation testing - Manager testing"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Types of user testing are :","level":1,"answers":["Alpha testing","Beta testing","All the answers are correct","Acceptance testing"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":3},{"question":"Which of the following from scrum master role","level":2,"answers":["Remove any impediments that abstruct a team's pursuit of its sprint goals","Defines goals for the overall project","Defines the sprint duration","Defines and prioritizes the requirments\/features"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":1},{"question":"Which of these are true for sprint backlog?","level":3,"answers":["Should be update every day","Should be update every year","Is created only by team members","The answers 1 & 3 are correct"],"team":"Panther","correct_ans":4}]}